<events><event><event_id>1</event_id><event_name>Box Cricket</event_name><introduction>Crazy about cricket, want to show off your cricketing skills then SPACE 2K15 gives you a chance to do so. BOX CRICKET is back with all its excitement. Do not miss the opportunity all the cricket loving crazy fans.</introduction><contact>Shivgovind : 09987388732
Sameer : 09757018790</contact><email /><category>Games And Sports</category><venue>Bhavans Ground</venue><prizes>Cash prize of Rs12000/- (Top 4 teams will be rewarded.)</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>1</event_id><event_name>A-MAZE-ING Rollers</event_name><introduction>Be the first to participate in the 1st time ever roller skating event organized in SPACE!!!
Skate, slide and weave between obstacles in a race against time. Find hidden objects other 
competitors cannot find. Survive the maze and win the prize.
A-MAZE-ING ROLLERS is a place where you will always be on a roll.

(THE EVENT IS ONLY FOR AMATEURS)The event consists of a maze which the participants have to traverse with roller skates within a stipulated time (5-7 mins). There will be obstacles to overcome and hidden objects for the participants to find in the maze. On the final day there will be a bonus round played between the prize winners of the 3 days. i.e. the 9 winning teams and a Grand Winner will be chosen.</introduction><contact>Neelotpal Roy-9820163394
Anjali Wani-9920823512
Rahul Palekar-9920020691
Kiran Ziware-9619288791
Apoorva Gosavi-9920779079</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPIT, 201 (FE IT)</venue><prizes>Per day: 300/- for winner
200/- for runner-up
100/- for 2nd runner-up
Bonus round winner will get 1000/-</prizes><rules>Some important points:
1.Full skating gear will be provided
2.Supports will be provided so no chance of falling down
3.4 mins time, so don't stop rolling
4.Come wearing shoes(any shoes will do)
5.Skates will be provided
</rules></event><event><event_id>1</event_id><event_name>Panel Debate</event_name><introduction>The Panel Debate is a chance to pit your speaking and convincing skills against some of the best debaters in the city.</introduction><contact>Varun 9930639228</contact><email /><category>Literary Arts</category><venue>In college campus</venue><prizes>Cash prizes of at least 4000 to be won</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>1</event_id><event_name>BeatBox</event_name><introduction>Participants have to give a solo performance for the duration of 3 minutes(approx). The winner will be decided by the jury according to the vocal skills of the competitors..</introduction><contact>Tanvi Jadhav - 9167415506
Zil Parmar - 8652377718
Pallavi Ghode - 7208768754</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>SP Quad</venue><prizes>Cash prize worth Rs: 1k/- for the winner.
Certificates for top three winners.</prizes><rules>1.Sound made by any organ of the body is allowed.
2.Fatal body contact will lead to immediate disqualification.</rules></event><event><event_id>2</event_id><event_name>Frisbee</event_name><introduction>The game is divided in a team of five and is 7 and 1/2 minutes for a half. You have to pass the frisbee from your goal area and catch it in your opponent's goal area to score a point. A player can hold the frisbee in his hand for max 10 sec failing which a foul will be given.You cannot run with the frisbee in your hand, at the most you can move a few steps.You can touch the frisbee only when it is in the air; once it touches the ground, your possession is lost immediately.</introduction><contact>Nemil-9920097393
Vaibhav-9619124266</contact><email /><category>Games And Sports</category><venue>Bhavans Ground</venue><prizes>Rs 1000 for the winning team</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>2</event_id><event_name>Antichess</event_name><introduction>The one who looses all the pieces first, wins the game.Force capture of pieces as and when possible.There are no checks in the game.King cannot castle in any case.King is like a normal piece.The game will be timed. Round 1 will be 10 minutes per player, Round 2 - 7 minutes per player hence forth all rounds including finals will be 5 minutes per player.

The game will in a tournament format. If possible as per the availability of the
participants, all rounds will take place on Day 1 itself or else the event may continue on Day 2 of SPACE-15 also. Final round will take place on Day 2 of SPACE-15.

Any player in case who wins a particular round and wishes to quit to tournament will be refunded 50% of the entry fee in case he quits after winning Round 1 or Round 2. If he quits after Round 3 or hence forth, then he will not be refunded.</introduction><contact>1. Rohit More - 9405177516
2. Parth Patni - 9833727266
3. Jay Trivedi - 9757340765</contact><email>patni.parth96@gmail.com</email><category>Informals</category><venue>SPIT Ground Floor, Opposite Workshop</venue><prizes>Prizes worth Rs.1,500.</prizes><rules>1. The one who looses all the pieces first, wins the game.
2. Force capture of pieces as and when possible.
3. There are no checks in the game.
4. King cannot castle in any case.
5. King is like a normal piece.
6. The game will be timed. Round 1 will be 10 minutes per player, Round 2 - 7 minutes per player hence forth all rounds including finals will be 5 minutes per player.</rules></event><event><event_id>2</event_id><event_name>Ouiz</event_name><introduction>The quiz is a college level General Quiz which will cover a wide range of topics. The quiz will not be only trivia based. Further details will be provided to the participants upon registering</introduction><contact>Nidheesh - 9920416931</contact><email /><category>Literary Arts</category><venue>In College Campus</venue><prizes>Prizes worth Rs 2.5k for winners
1 k for runners up. Prizes for all finalists.</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>2</event_id><event_name>Dance Ovation</event_name><introduction>Do a loony goony dance,-Across the dance floor,-Put something special in the world,-That ain't been there before!-Here's inviting you to tap ur feet to the rhythm.... Jive Jitterbug kathak hip-hop-It just take two to tango or one to solo n sizzle d floor!!-All u need to do is include the theme 'Element' in ur dance form!( any 1 element is okay )</introduction><contact>Saumya- 9757019536
Surabhi- 9773461563
Tamara- 9167705585
Hansraj- 8805828259</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>Solo: 1st- worth Rs.2000/-, 2nd- worth Rs.1500/-
Duet: worth Rs.2000/-</prizes><rules>For-Elimination round - 15 Feb-Dance - 1 to 1&amp;1.5 min only-Theme - any 1 elements should be there ..Rules for final event i.e. on 1 march-Dance - 3 min-CD and PD participants have to bring-Reporting time - 9-Theme - any 1 element should be there</rules></event><event><event_id>3</event_id><event_name>Lagori</event_name><introduction>The game is between two teams of 5 members each involving a ball and a pile of flat stones. A member of one team (the seekers) throws a soft ball at a pile of stones to knock them over. The seekers then try to restore the pile of stones while the opposing team (the hitters) throw the ball at them. If the ball touches a seeker, he is out and his team continues without him. But a team member can always safeguard himself by touching the opposite team member before the ball hits him.The seekers cannot cross the boundary. If any of the seekers crosses it then he is out.If the person trying to knock down the pile cannot do it in three tries then he is out.In any of the three tries, if the thrower's ball does not knock down the pile and is caught by an opponent after the first bounce then the thrower is out.If the thrower's ball bounces off the pile and an opponent catches it then the thrower's whole team is out.If the seekers succeed in restoring the pile then they can use the point scored to buy back their ousted team mate.
If the opponent player hits the ball on the leg of throwers and his/her team, then all the players are out.
Registration fees : 20/- per person
</introduction><contact>Neelesh-9892553124
Ganesh-9870450100</contact><email /><category>Games And Sports</category><venue>Bhavans Ground</venue><prizes>Cash prize Rs 1000 for winning team</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>3</event_id><event_name>Bazinga</event_name><introduction>Your objective is to have fun, play with friend, brag about your skills by winning prizes! Come play the game of chance and skill at Bazinga! where between winning and losing lies fun.
Ring toss
Good at making things fall right into your circle? Well, here's something where your never-used skills may come in handy :P Grab n throw loops to rope in a snack or two as you go along... ;) 

Yummm.. :D

Balloon darts

You think you got game or a really good aim? Come on in and bang those balloons right off the wall in this fun and thrilling event and win something cool for yourself...

Ping pong toss

Not that good a TT player? No worries, you still have the right to grab hold of those ping pong balls :P

Try out this fun game where you've got to try and bounce the balls right into a cup (rules regarding the number of bounces, etc. shall be explained to you). So go ahead, enjoy!

Knock 'em down

Good at throwing stuff at people? A bit angry with your latest results? :P Fret not! Aim those cans and knock each of 'em right out! But, be careful not to knock someone's head off :P

Drop 'em right

Playing bouncy balls has always been fun, eh? Well, try and beat this game (of course, unless it beats the c*** out of you). A difficult, off-beat, yet fun-to-play game, try and get those balls to bounce right into place! All you've gotta do is DROP 'EM RIGHT!!</introduction><contact>Kshitij Nagvekar - 7738122781
Ferina Patel - 9664003863</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>VolleyBall Court</venue><prizes>Subway vouchers, goodies, key-chains, etc</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>3</event_id><event_name>SP MUN</event_name><introduction>
Sardar Patel Model United Nations 2015
The Second Edition

Theme - The Changing Paradigm

Formal attire ( Suit up guys for the battle isnt just verbal!)

--AGENDA

-DISEC
1. Containing the threat of ISIS in Iraq and Syria.
2. The Situation in Crimea

-ECOFIN
1. Setting up of an alternative universal currency 
2. Financial security in cyber space

-HRC
1. Human Rights violations by ISIS against Iraqi and Syrian civilians
2. Addressing the rights of HIV-AIDS patients and their elevation from discriminatory violations


--EXECUTIVE BOARD for SPMUN 2015

-First Committee
DISARMAMENT AND INTERNATIONAL SECURITY COMMITTEE(DISEC)
Chair - Rishabh Srivastava 
Co-Chair - Ishaan Sharma

-Second Committee
ECONOMIC AND FINANCIAL COMMITTEE (ECOFIN)
Chair - Rahul Jawahrani
Co-Chair - Aman Johri

-Third Committee
HUMAN RIGHTS COUNCIL (HRC)
Chair - Chaitanya Parsana
Co-Chair - Aditi Puthran

Fb page - 
https://m.facebook.com/spitmun

Sp Mun website - www.spmun2.wordpress.com

Registration fees - Rs. 1000/-</introduction><contact>Chaitanya -9820010951
Rohit --9920824695</contact><email /><category>Literary Arts</category><venue>In College Campus</venue><prizes>Worth 30,000/- Up For Grabs!</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>3</event_id><event_name>High Octane</event_name><introduction>High octane is the band event of SPACE. Come and take part in the adrenaline raising event in which you get to compete with the country's finest bands and also share the stage with the metal monsters ZYGNEMA.

Register here:-http://goo.gl/forms/H2MAOmlb4p</introduction><contact>Aashay - 9167449114
Alan - 9821489033</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>Worth Rs. 10000/-</prizes><rules>1. No foul language, indecent behaviour/lyrics would be tolerated
2. Performing bands must accept the slot provided to them.
3. No cigarettes or narcotic substances will be allowed in the college premises.
4. No eatables, bottles, deodorants, Sharp objects will be allowed.
5. Participants will be responsible for any loss/damage of equipments provided to them by the organizers.</rules></event><event><event_id>4</event_id><event_name>LAN Gaming</event_name><introduction>"Hushed voices, silent footsteps, reload of a gun, reviving of engines, a gush of nitrous." If all this is music to your ears then you belong here at the ultimate gaming arcade for the maniacs who just can-t get enough of reality.
LAN GAMING at SPACE'15 is getting geared up to be the biggest LAN gaming event this year. 

FIFA'14, Counter-Strike 1.6, Need for Speed-Most Wanted, its all here. Counter-Strike is the oldest, and most popular - consequently the bar for this game is set very high - the moment you blink, you are gone. Then here's FIFA'14 for football freaks. Can't play it on the field? So what! Experience it virtually and feel the same pressure that players experience on the field.
For those who love to ride monsters and rule the roads, this event gives you the golden opportunity , play NFSMW and prove you are the king here.</introduction><contact>Rohit Roongta : +91-9324559862 ( FIFA )
Pratik Velhal : +91 97029 16148? ( CS 1.6 )
Saurabh Pachpande : +91 81493 13363? ( NFS )</contact><email /><category>Games And Sports</category><venue>SPIT</venue><prizes>Worth upto Rs.17000</prizes><rules>GENERAL RULES:
These rules apply to everyone attending. They can be changed without notice.
1. You are responsible for your actions and equipment. We are not liable for anything that happens to you and your equipment.
2. Do not attempt to steal items from the event or anyone else. Legal consequences will be there.
3. Cheating is not tolerated.
4. Do not bring any type of hacks/viruses/etc. to the event.
5. Listen to those in charge.
6. We reserve the right to remove anyone from premises for any reason we fit.
For more details - contact organizers
</rules></event><event><event_id>4</event_id><event_name>Casino</event_name><introduction>'Casino Royale' is the event of SPACE 2015 which will let you explore your gambling wits.So don't miss this opportunity to make some extra cash and have amazing time while at it! This event includes games like poker, black jack, roulette, deal ya no deal and also 7up 7 down!</introduction><contact>Yash Jain-9819693626.</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE - Room 235, Electrical Drawing Hall</venue><prizes>NA</prizes><rules>Contact Organizer For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>4</event_id><event_name>Instrumental Wars</event_name><introduction>Instrumental Wars gives you a golden opportunity to show your instrumental talent and fill the magic in air with your instrumental grace. The duration of performance would be 5 to 7 minutes. 

There will be gap of 10 to 15 minutes between two performances for further preparation. Results would be declared by the respective judges and results would be based on points gained by participants.

Note: Participants have to bring their own instruments for performance.</introduction><contact>Tejashree Gore-8097291471
Apoorva Raut-9975041346
Gauri Joshi-9757260184</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>1500/-</prizes><rules>The rule sheet will be handed out to the teams. 
No. of participants in a team : 4+2</rules></event><event><event_id>5</event_id><event_name>Rink Football</event_name><introduction>Space Rink Football is an open tournament organised at Bhavans ground.
Registration fee: 500/-</introduction><contact>Vrajesh- 9769929866
Parth- 8767326335
Mitul- 9820765652</contact><email /><category>Games And Sports</category><venue>Bhavans Ground</venue><prizes>Cash 8k  winners
Cash 4k runners up                       
Top 8 awarded</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>5</event_id><event_name>Find The Way</event_name><introduction>Fed up of lectures and attendance ???

Looking for a way out? Here's your chance! We have an exciting fun-filled game just for u ;-)

Use your sixth sense to get through this maddening maze of twists and turns...

Oh!...and you'll be blind ;p

No GPS, map or compass to help you...

Your partner's voice is your only choice...!</introduction><contact>Sneha - 8082489792
Riddhi - 7208459361</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE Parking Space</venue><prizes>Rs. 50/-</prizes><rules>-participants will be in pairs, though more than one pair may be taken at a time
-one person will be blind-folded and the other person will guide his friend's way
- task should be completed within the given time</rules></event><event><event_id>5</event_id><event_name>Mr. &amp; Ms. SPACE</event_name><introduction>Do you think you have what it takes to bag the most coveted title of SPACE ??? Are you confident enough to believe you can beat every single person out there ??

Then it's time to register for Mr n Miss SPACE .

Participants have to go through multiple rounds which will test their wit , composure and ability to present themselves in an amicable way in all sorts of situations. This event attempts to test your whole personality from various perspective .

So gear up guys!!

THE HUNT IS ON !!!!</introduction><contact>Harshit(Spce) -8888571923
Mokshada(spit)-8087924584</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle (Sabhagriha)</venue><prizes>Worth Rs. 1500 /-</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>6</event_id><event_name>Sumo Mania</event_name><introduction>After all that fun last year, the sumos are back!!!
SPACE 2015 ,the annual cultural extravaganza of SPCE &amp; SPIT presents -" SUMO MANIA " .
The one and only place to complete your dreams of fighting like sumos.
This is a FUN event ...
SUMO MANIA is a competitive full contact wrestling fun sport ,where a wrestler attempts to force another wrestler out of a circular ring or to touch the ground 
with anything other than the soles of the feet.

The sumos are waiting.

So how big you wanna fight???</introduction><contact>Shreyash - 9867124555
Prince----- --9768847126</contact><email /><category>Games And Sports</category><venue>Temple Area (Stage)</venue><prizes>NA</prizes><rules>1) Each game comprises of three rounds.
2) In each round the sumo either tries to throw his opponent out of the ring or make him fall on the ground.</rules></event><event><event_id>6</event_id><event_name>Hogathon</event_name><introduction>The Hogathon is taking an activity you love, and turning it into a competition.

Face off with all your friends and find out who can gulp down the maximum amount in the fastest time in three high intensity rounds.

The only event in which you can -win a prize by eating your favourite food.</introduction><contact>Faizaan-09920483623
Sonali- 09930212995</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE entrance.</venue><prizes>Amazing prizes to be won!!</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>6</event_id><event_name>Nukkad</event_name><introduction>The most awaited Cultural Festival of- SPCE &amp; SPIT -SPACE- is back with loads n loads of prizes!!!!

Theme - ELEMENTS

SPACE presents NUKKAD-Street Play

Everyone is a Fantastic actor in some way or the other !
This is the time U show it to d world!
So get on ur Acting Masks!! Prepare a script &amp; Show us what You've got.

-&gt;The competition will be conducted on an 360degree Open Stage.
-&gt;No microphones, speakers, Music system will be allowed or available.
-&gt;Teams can sing/dance by themselves to create the necessary music or sound however, Dholak and Duff can be used.

-&gt;Teams using any Props/Costumes/Dresses must bring all their requirements and must be ready well in time as per instructions of the organizer however the name of the college should not be displayed on the dresses in any form .

-&gt;No props or costume or any material will be provided by the host college.

-&gt;No time for stage setting will be given during the competition.

-&gt;Five minutes buffer time can b used for setting props --

-&gt;Use of expletives may be allowed with prior clarification with Coordinators.

-&gt;The theme of the street play should be socially relevant and highlight social issues.

-&gt;The contestants are strictly advised not to disclose the name of their college/Institution to the Jury members/audience while introducing themselves on the stage.

-&gt;Street play asks you to provide your name and e-mail address when entering a contest.The information we collect will not be shared with any other organization.Street play may use your e-mail address to send informational material about the site; you can opt out of receiving e-mail about anything other than a contest you've entered by including that preference in your entry (if appropriate) or by e-mailing.</introduction><contact>ADITI-9930470006
ARJUN-9920801847
ANKITA-9969205330
ROHINI-8237188108</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>SP QUADRANGLE</venue><prizes>1st Prize- worth 3000/-
Best Actor Prize- worth 500/-</prizes><rules>-&gt;Time Limit :Time allowed to each team is minimum 10 mins. and maximum 12 mins.

Warning Bell : 10 Mins
Final Bell :12 Mins Teams (exceeding 12 mins. will attract negative marking.)

-&gt;Language of the Play : Teams to use Hindi or Marathi as the language of the play. Partial English can be used.

-&gt;Two teams per college are allowed but members should not be repeated.

-&gt;The uniformity in the dress is must.

-&gt;Use of vulgar language is prohibited.Points may be deducted for the same based on Judge-s discretion.

-&gt;Final 6 teams will qualify.

-&gt;The organizing Committee reserves the right to change the venue, time and rules, if desired.

-&gt;Decision of judges will be final and binding on all teams.</rules></event><event><event_id>7</event_id><event_name>The Amazing Race</event_name><introduction>The Era Of "The Amazing Race" Is Back With More Fun,Frolic &amp; Excitement
Gear Up Your Shoes And Those Tangling Laces For The Most-Talked-About
Event Of S.P.A.C.E.
Our Very Own " The Amazing Race"
You Think You Know "Aamchi Mumbai" Well ?
We Dont Think So.

Here's A Platform To Prove Us Wrong  And To Walk Away With A Plethora

Of Exciting Prizes.

Do Participate In Large Numbers.!</introduction><contact>Yash : 9819693626.
Niharika :9920209857.
Prince :9768847126.</contact><email /><category>Innovations</category><venue>Starting Point - Quadrangle,SPCE</venue><prizes>Exciting Prices Worth Rs 6000</prizes><rules>1) Use of private vehicles is Strictly Prohibited. If found using private transport during the race, the team will be  disqualified immediately.

2) Use only Public Transport such as Auto, Taxi , Best buses ,Local Trains, Metro  etc.

3) Participants must have internet connection active on their smartphones.

4) Participants must have a QR code and bar code scanner.</rules></event><event><event_id>7</event_id><event_name>Hogwarts Express</event_name><introduction>Explore the magical world of Harry Potter through a series of mind boggling quizzes and fun games. Wield your wands and unleash the magic.</introduction><contact>Ved Soni: 9867206870
Rohit Bhave: 9920164450</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE - Room 233 BE Electricals</venue><prizes>Exciting goodies to be won</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>7</event_id><event_name>RangManch</event_name><introduction>All world is a stage n all men and women are merely players, so act well your part and there the honor lies-.So you have the freedom to choose your idea and present it to fascinate the audience.</introduction><contact>Prachi: +919820466349
Akshata: +919867286529
Dhanashree: +919820090824
Monika: +918657119295</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>Cash Prizes of around Rs.3000/- for best drama</prizes><rules>1) Time Limit:15-20 mins
2) Theme-of your choice
3) Need to submit outline (softcopy) of their drama specifying Title, Characters, Author.
4) Language- English, Hindi, Marathi.
5) Please bring your own props. Mics and Speakers will be provided.
6) The participants need to abide by the judge-s decision which shall be final.</rules></event><event><event_id>8</event_id><event_name>Karaoke</event_name><introduction>"Thande Thande pani se nahana chahiye..Gaana aaye ya na aaye gaana chahiye !! "
Are you a bathroom singer or star singer?? Karaoke is for everyone..
Don't be shy,give it a try !!
Day filled with Music,Masti and fun..
Come out of your shell and sing your heart out..
Bring your friends on 27th and 28th february,Sing your favorite song and win exciting prizes!!

Rounds:
Open for everyone
Goodies for the one who sing decently
There will be mega challenge which will be declared on event day itself -,winner will get grand prize</introduction><contact>Vishal-8983218110
Ash-9665720881</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>Spit (Near lift)</venue><prizes>Goodies for the one who sing decently
Winner will get grand prize</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>8</event_id><event_name>Street Dance</event_name><introduction>Set the streets ablaze with your passion. Turn the opposition into a mere speck of dust as you weave your way through the patterns of space-time to rise above everyone else! Feel the pump as you blend into the various elemental illusions of dance. So come over and break free!</introduction><contact>Aishwarya Kulkarni- 9769779026.
Abhay Sundesha- 9930446630.
Hetal Chavan- 9167726333.</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle.</venue><prizes>Prizes worth up to Rs.5000/-</prizes><rules>Team size: 6-15.
ROUNDS:
ELIMINATION.
FINALE.
FACE-OFF.
TIME LIMIT:  6-10 minutes (+2 min set-up time)
JUDGING CRITERIA: Choreography, Energy, Synchronization, Stage utilization, Costumes, Innovation, Overall impact.</rules></event><event><event_id>9</event_id><event_name>Laser Maze 2.0</event_name><introduction>The participant has to cross a room full of intricate web of lasers. At the end of the room the participant has to steal the Diamond kept there. Once this is done the participant has to return back to the place from where he/she started. The room will have a fog machine to make the laser beam more visible. Proper eye gear will also be provided to the participant to avoid any kind of damage to eyes. 

THIS TIME THE CHALLENGE GETS BIGGER AND BETTER THAN EVER BEFORE...!! 
SO COME - PROVE YOUR METTLE AND ROB THE VAULT..!!</introduction><contact>Garvit Bhatt-9619081974</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>S.P.I.T Gymkhana</venue><prizes>Amazing Cash Prizes to be won...!!</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>9</event_id><event_name>Swaranjali</event_name><introduction>"Where words fail , music speaks" Come and sing your heart out and win great prizes.


</introduction><contact>Madhura 8689877231
Suyash-- 99 87 432421
Sanjana +91 90 04 379724</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>Winners:
1K Cash solo- 1.5K Cash duet
Runners Up:- worth Rs 500.</prizes><rules>solo and duet singing-

1. Elimination rounds on 15/2/15 . Participants can sing a hindi marathi or english song having a duration of 3-4.5 minutes
2.Those who qualify will compete In the final event.
3.Participants should try n bring their own instruments/instrumentalist or karaoke track.
4.The participants need to abide by the judge's decision which shall be final.

NOTE:

1.participants can take part in both the categories (solo and duet)
2.karaoke at the time of elims is optional</rules></event><event><event_id>10</event_id><event_name>Lost In Space</event_name><introduction>The next level of 'TECH-MAZE'

Team of 2 players.
-first player will be handed over with a remote control car and he will be blind-folded.

-the other player will assist the first playerBy guiding him properly to reach the centre of CIRCULAR maze.

-the most amazing thing about the event is that it will take place in a dark room and only maze will be visible as it is outlined with radium strips .

-so the game is in your hands . Let's see how much your co-ordination works .

-As per the theme of 'SPACE' this time the level of event is going to be very different which includes different elements.

So be ready to ROLL!

The most amazing and different event of SPACE .
</introduction><contact>Kunal 8149648831</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE - Room 234 TE Electricals </venue><prizes>On the spot</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>10</event_id><event_name>Visual Impact</event_name><introduction>One person can dance but a group can break the stage! For all those with fierce spirits in your minds and the burning passion , SPACE- presents to you The Visual Impact -A Group Dance competition where all the 5 elements of the nature come together . The only way to make your power show is to plunge into the rhythm , move with it and dance! Let the rhythm change your world on the floor!</introduction><contact>Riddhi Chabhadhia - 9930878154
Apakrita Tayade - 9029332972</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>Worth Rs.8000</prizes><rules>1.No revealing costumes. 
2.Song duration must be within 7minutes
3.No profanity is to be heard.
4.Every group must consist of max 18members. No substitution permitted.
5.Use of drugs, cigarettes and alcoholic beverage are strictly prohibited.
6.Please prepare your own CD, groups must register at the location 45 minutes before thecompetition start. 
7.Every participant must be college/university student. 
8.Deadline for registration: 20th feb 2015. 
9.The dance style should include any form of dance. 
10.No explicit gestures, comments and movements. 
11.Marks will be given on creativity, music, stage presence, teamwork, dance 
variation,synchronization, entertainment value, crowd response and skills. The decisions of the judgesare final.</rules></event><event><event_id>11</event_id><event_name>Minute To Win It</event_name><introduction>- Team of 2 players
- Each team will be given a task and it should be completed in one minute
- If task is successfully completed then next task will be provided
- Team completing 5 tasks in a row will win prizes Rs. 500 worth
-So get ready to win Rs.500 in 5 minutes.
-Lets see how fast you are!</introduction><contact>Sumit Pawar 9503620300
Mohak Patel 8237716777
Mahesh Khedekar 9422179666</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE Entrance</venue><prizes>Team completing 5 tasks in a row will win prizes Rs. 500 worth. So get ready to win Rs.500 in 5 minutes</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>11</event_id><event_name>War Of Branches</event_name><introduction>Behold! The most anticipated, the most renowned and the grandest event of SPACE'15 is here!!! War Of Branches- the only Intra College Dance Battle.
8 Branches-1 Winner. Do you think your branch is THE CHOSEN ONE?</introduction><contact>Shivangi-09819229863
Jasraj-09158285232
Sunidhi-09665637191</contact><email /><category>Performing Arts</category><venue>Sp Quadrangle</venue><prizes>Exciting rewards awaiting its deserving owner</prizes><rules>1.Contestants must be ready to perform when called.-They alone are responsible for not missing their turn.-
2.Judges- decisions are final, and they will not be-required to explain standing.
3. Maximum no. of teams per branch-1 
4. Maximum no. of people on stage at a time -15 .
5. Maximum time limit- 7mins.
6. Use of props is mandatory. 
7. Deadline for registration is 10th February,2015.
8. Dress and appearances will be considered.
9. Competitors must arrive 30 minutes before the beginning of the event.
10. No form of liquid, gel, aerosol, glitter may be used that can adversely affect the dancing surface.
11. Any participant found vandalizing or causing a disruption at the competition is subject to disqualification and/or liable for payment of repairs
12. Competitors are expected to demonstrate good sportsmanship and general support to ALL participants
13. If music is inappropriate, the adjudicators have a right to deduct marks from that routine.

Its not just a dance battle, its THE Fight for your pride!
Everything is fair in love and war and this is WAR!</rules></event><event><event_id>12</event_id><event_name>Neon Room</event_name><introduction>"Bring on the neon this world cup season" 
This experience is unparalleled taking you on an amazing adrenaline-filled adventure ,guaranteed to blow your mind and reactivate your senses.It is a unique event that fuses together sports and special effects into a mind blowing combination which creates excitement and enjoyment start to finish........</introduction><contact>Parth-9821231654
Aditya-9920260951</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPIT Room No. 202 and 203</venue><prizes>Cash prizes and vouchers to be won</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>13</event_id><event_name>Pool Table</event_name><introduction>Play Pool for 20mins.It will be a knock out.
Rules will be put up on the day of event itself.</introduction><contact>Madhura-9769672332
Keyur-9867686962
Leenita-8692944557
Prathamesh-9619177272</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>Temple Area</venue><prizes>1K</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>14</event_id><event_name>Quadra Twist</event_name><introduction>TWISTER HOOPLAH:
The Twister with a twist.-
Get a partner along and be twisted between the rings!
Spin the wheel and put the ring between you and your partner and compete-with-the opposite team till either of the teams drops-a

MUSICAL CHAIRS WITH A TWIST:

The blindfolded Musical Chairs is here.
Compete with your partner against the opposite team.
Just like our favourite Musical Chairs... although you get to fight, push, grapple-and dance-to the music as you find a-chair to sit-on all while being blindfolded.

REVERSE PICTIONARY:

Draw a picture for your partner - ... but verbally. Be blindfolded as the partner draws and tries guessing -the movie-.

Tip of the day:-Efficiency-and accuracy will take you a long way-in this-pictionary!

WIRE LOOP GAME:

The traditional game of guiding the metal loop along the serpentine length of the game without actually touching the wire.</introduction><contact>Maitri-9820174628
Sanskruti-9769243280</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPIT, Room: 207</venue><prizes>Exciting prizes to be won</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>16</event_id><event_name>Slow Cycling</event_name><introduction>Racing Your Cycles At A Higher Pace Has Always Been Quite An Easier Stuff To Do.
But,Maintaining Your Bike At A Tortoise Pace Is A Gruesome Job.Here,The One Who Finishes Last Amongst The Contenders Bags The Prize!

Shocking Isn't It ?

So Lets Gear Up Together For The Amazing "Slow Cycle Race"!

P.S: CYCLES WILL BE PROVIDED.
</introduction><contact>Yash-9819693626
Ferina-9664003863</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>Ahead of volleyball court.</venue><prizes>Exciting vouchers to be won</prizes><rules>1.You Cannot Cross Lanes.
2.Cant Keep Your Feet Down. (Once,Its Ok..Twice,You're Busted)</rules></event><event><event_id>17</event_id><event_name>Space Open 2015 - Rubik's Cube</event_name><introduction /><contact>Abhijit Zimare  -  9769586462</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE - Room 221, Mechanical Drawing Hall</venue><prizes>Medals and Certificates to the winners
Certificates are signed by WCA Delegate.
Organizers retain rights to decide exact cash prizes
Prizes may include cash, gift coupons and puzzles.</prizes><rules>As per WCA rules
Every competitor is expected to know and comply with ALL WCA Regulations. Some important 

ones are listed below :

1e2 - Every competitor must be available for judging. If he or she is required for judging, a competitor may be excused only for a legitimate reason (eg. Being umfamiliar with the puzzle) , at the discretion of the Delegate. Penalty : Disqualification from tge competition (See. Reg 2k)

2f. Competitors must obey venue rules and caonduct themselves in a considerate manner.

2g. Competitors accompanied with guests must remain quiet inside the designated competition area. Talking is permitted but must be kept at a reasonable level and away from competitor actively participating.

2i. While competing, competitors must not use electronics or audio gadgets.

2k. The WCA Delegate may disqualify the competitor from all the events of the 
competition if the competitor 

2k1) Fails to check in or register in time for the competition.

2n3 The competitor must accept all final rulings of the delegate. 
Penalty : Disqualification from the competition

3a. Competitorsust provide their own puzzles fror the competiton

3a1. Comperitors must be ready when their round is called for the competition. Penalty : Disqualification

3j Puzzles must be clean and must not have any markings damage, elevated pieces, or any differences that significantly distinguishes any piece with any other similar piece. Exception : A logo (See regulation 3)

5b If a puzzle defect occurs during a solve the participant may choose to either repair the defect and continue the attempt or to stop the attempt

5c+ If a competitor has a puzzle defect, this does not give him a right of an extra attempt.

7b Spectators must remain atleast 1.5 meters away from solving stations when they are in use

A1c A competitor participating in an event must fulfill the event's requirements (e.g. knowing how to solve the puzzle. A competitor competing with the expectation of a DNF may be disqualified from the event with the discretion of the delegate.

A5a. While inspecting or solving the competitor must not communicate with anyhody else other than the judge. Penalty : DNF , Disqualification for the attempt

A6b The competitor is responsible for stopping stackmat timer correctly. 

Event List - 
2x2
3x3 One Handed
3x3
3x3 Blind Folded
4x4
Pyraminx</rules></event><event><event_id>18</event_id><event_name>SP Sherlock</event_name><introduction>Mystery solving just got better with you as Sherlock!!

Investigate a crime scene like Sherlock, deducing clues as you discover the intriguing mystery behind the crime scene. The mystery gets more interesting with every clue you deduce!! With every clue, you take a plunge deeper into the mystery, as the complexity gets a notch higher giving you an adrenaline rush!! So you think you're smart enough to be the next Sherlock Holmes??

Let's find it out!!
Entry fees : 20/-</introduction><contact>Jay-9930177118
Niket-9664315911</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE Entrance</venue><prizes>Sherlock merchandise and few surprises awaits you...</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>19</event_id><event_name>Talaash</event_name><introduction>A criminal's illusion of " the perfect crime" would have never been proved imperfect had it notbeen for the adept detectives. So here's a chance to decode one such thriller and explore the operative (or detective) within you.

Let's crack the strenuous cases together in our event "TALAASH-crime scene- investigation"-

Do talaash in our very own bhavan's campus.- Hunt for clues , solve them , identify the murderer- and-WIN EXCITING PRIZES!</introduction><contact>Shubham: 8275567296
Mrdvika:9833879201</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>Bhavans Campus</venue><prizes>Worth Rs 5k</prizes><rules>Contact organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>20</event_id><event_name>The Elemental Quest</event_name><introduction>Bored of your daily routine? Looking for some fun time with friends??? Then your wait is over..!! 

SPCE-SPIT

SPACE 2K15 brings to you...THE ELEMENTAL QUEST!

A fun-filled competition where your quest to win involves a clue-based journey with a new and more enjoyable task to perform at every stage leading you to a grand prize of Rs. 1.5k!!</introduction><contact>Smriti -- 9969275863
Surabhi - 9820941429
Soukhya - 7738314954</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>SPCE Quad</venue><prizes>Upto Rs. 1.5K</prizes><rules>Contact Organizers For Rules</rules></event><event><event_id>21</event_id><event_name>B-Boying Workshop</event_name><introduction>B-boying, also called breakdancing, is a style of street dance that originated among African American and Puerto Rican youths in New York City. Learn this amazing form of dance here at SPACE'15 from expert Street Dancers. So for all the enthusiastic dancers of MUMBAI , who want to have a breathtaking experience, this is the place to be.
Registration fees: 100/- per head</introduction><contact>Omkar - 9930092715
Suraj- 9820629655</contact><email /><category>Workshops</category><venue>FE Civil (SPCE)</venue><prizes>For details contact organizers</prizes><rules>For details contact organizers</rules></event><event><event_id>22</event_id><event_name>War of DJs</event_name><introduction>A State Level DJ Battlefield for all budding DJs..!
Here's a Platform to Showcase Your Talent..!
Judged by renowned DJ Surr

Registration fees: 1000/-</introduction><contact>Sagar +919867914842</contact><email /><category>Informals</category><venue>In College Campus</venue><prizes>For details contact organizers</prizes><rules>1. The console provided will be Pioneer CDJ 2000 NXS with a Pioneer DJ Mixer 600 / 900.
2. Each participant will get 10 minutes of round to show his or her DJing skills.
3. Music will be played in USB record box supported.
4. Each participant should carry his/her USB drive.
5. Every participant's USB drive will be verified before use.
6. USB must be formatted and should ONLY CONTAIN music participant is going to play and mix. No other data should be present or else participant will not be allowed to play.
7. In 10 minutes of time each participant has to mix minimum 10 tracks. Time can be extended at the time of event according to the situation.
8. No pre remixes / DJ tag mixes will be allowed.
9. If a participant wants to play with CDs, then the CDs should be NEWLY BURNED and should only contain music he/she is going to play and mix. CDs should NOT CONTAIN any other data than the music required for the event. Each participant has to use minimum 4 CDs in the whole 10 minute round. CDs should be scratch-less and brand new.
10. Judge's decision will be final.
11. It would be better if every participant also carries CDs in order to be on the safer side if some technical issues occur with USB.
</rules></event><event><event_id>23</event_id><event_name>Short Film Making</event_name><introduction>Lights..! Camera..! Action..!
Registration fees : 150/-
Upload your videos on :-
www.facebook.com/spacethefest
</introduction><contact>Vinay +918097631355
Darshan +919870909419</contact><email /><category>Innovations</category><venue>SPIT - Room No. 403</venue><prizes>Prizes worth Rs5000</prizes><rules>Rules for short film:

1. The film should not be more than 5 minutes.
2. Subtitles are compulsory.
3. Film should not offend any group or person in terms of movie cast or music
4. Music if adopted or borrowed from someone should be mentioned.
5. Plagiarism is strictly prohibited.
6. Final decision of selection or screening would be that of the organisers.
7. Anyone who violates the above mentioned rules can be disqualified.

Deadline of posting videos online
26th February 2015 11.59 pm
</rules></event><event><event_id>24</event_id><event_name>Wall Painting</event_name><introduction>Time to get those paint brushes out and unveil the artist in you.
Come and paint the walls of our college and transform it into your very own masterpiece.
SPACE'15 invites you to voice your thoughts through WALL PAINTING.</introduction><contact>Vinay +918097631355
Darshan +919870909419</contact><email /><category>Innovations</category><venue>SPIT Entrance</venue><prizes>-</prizes><rules>-</rules></event></events>

